<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalProject</string>
    <string name="strDepartment">Department:</string>
    <string name="strQuarter">Quarter:</string>
    <string name="strCourse">Course:</string>
    <string name="strItem">Item:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_basic">BasicActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="queryString">[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"110","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"COMPUTER PRGRM PYTHON","courseDescription":"A general introduction to concepts related to designing and writing computer programs and procedures. Students learn to apply programming logic and problem-solving techniques, algorithmic thinking, and concepts such as data types and data structures using Python.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: ENGL 093 (or placement into ENGL 099 or higher) and MATH 090 (or placement into MATH 099 or higher)","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"110","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R1","itemNbr":9630,"days":"MW","timeLocation":"12:00 PM - 01:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Zerrouki M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"111","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"COMPUTER PROG FUNDAMENTL","courseDescription":"A general introduction to concepts related to designing and writing computer programs and procedures. Students study problem-solving techniques, algorithmic thinking, programming logic, and concepts such as data types, data structures, and object-oriented programming.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: MATH 090 (or placement into MATH 099 or higher) and ENGL 093 (or placement into ENGL 099 or higher)","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"111","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R1","itemNbr":9635,"days":"MW","timeLocation":"04:00 PM - 05:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Zerrouki M","labFee":85.0},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"111","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R2","itemNbr":9640,"days":"TTh","timeLocation":"12:00 PM - 01:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Zerrouki M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"112","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"HTML AND CSS","courseDescription":"This course is an introduction to HyperText Markup Language (HTML) and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS).  Students examine the key components of HTML to create functional web pages and apply CSS style sheets to improve page layout and overall appearance. Class teaches elements of responsive web design and techniques of its implementation.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CSD 110 or CSD 111 (or concurrent enrollment in either course) or completion of one of the following: BTE 120, DSGN 100, or CSNT 115. MATH 087 (or placement into MATH 090 or higher) and ENGL 093 (or placement info ENGL 099 or higher). Students who completed ITAD 111 meet the CSD 111 prerequisite. Students who completeD MMDP 101 or DSGN 101 meet the DSGN 100 prerequisite.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"112","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"L1","itemNbr":9645,"days":"ARRANGED","timeLocation":"@ ONLNE","instructor":"Dion D","labFee":85.0},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"112","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R1","itemNbr":9650,"days":"TTh","timeLocation":"09:00 AM - 11:50 AM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Dion D","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"122","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"JAVASCRIPT AND JQUERY","courseDescription":"Students learn to apply programming skills to build dynamic, interactive web pages and web applications. Students use JavaScript and jQuery to manipulate the Browser Object Model, validate forms, use object-oriented techniques, and enhance website usability and user experience by adding dynamic features to the HTML pages.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"When enrolling into this class, students are expected to know HTML and CSS syntax, basic programming control structures (loops and if-else statements), and be familiar with array manipulation and function-writing techniques in programming language of their choice. Prerequisites: CSD 112 and CSD 111 or 110 Students who completed ITAD 111 and ITAD 112 meet the prerequisites.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"122","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9655,"days":"T","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Mai D","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"138","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"SQL","courseDescription":"Students will learn how to use Structured Query Language (SQL) to retrieve information from a relational database, filter, modify, group and summarize data, and retrieve joint information from multiple tables in a database.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: CSD 111 or CSD 110 Students who completed ITAD 111 meet the prerequisite.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"138","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9660,"days":"W","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Zerrouki M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"228","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"PROGRAMMING WITH C#","courseDescription":"C# is a modern, powerful, and expressive object-oriented language that is widely used in general software development as well as web development. Students learn the language fundamentals and more advanced topics including inheritance, event-driven programming, and GUI implementation.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: CS\u0026 141","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"228","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9685,"days":"M","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Blackwell P","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"233","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"C++ PROGRAMMING","courseDescription":"This class teaches C++ programming language, its specific features, and the advantages they present for software development. The topics include pointers and memory management, reference parameters, c-strings and arrays as primitive data types, class inheritance, polymorphism, encapsulation, use of virtual functions and templates, and exceptions.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: CSD 143 (may also be taken as a corequisite) Students who completed CS 143 meet the prerequisite.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"233","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9690,"days":"Th","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Ferguson D","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"235","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"ALGORITHMS \u0026 DATA STRUCT","courseDescription":"Students study data structures, such as stacks, queues, hash tables, heaps, trees, and graphs, and use different algorithmic approaches to problem solving, such as simple recursion, backtracking, divide and conquer, greedy and brute force algorithms, and dynamic programming. Students analyze algorithm efficiency in terms of memory use and speed, using Big O notation for run-time performance estimation.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: Faculty advisor permission only","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"235","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9695,"days":"T","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Abbott T","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"268","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"QA METHODOLOGIES","courseDescription":"This Quality Assurance (QA) Methodologies course is an introduction to the theory, concepts, and reasoning behind software testing and automation. Students learn how to create and run test scripts and implement basic test projects.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: CS\u0026 141","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"268","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"L1","itemNbr":9697,"days":"ARRANGED","timeLocation":":   AM -   :   AM @ ONLNE","instructor":"GuerraHahn,M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"275","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"PHP SCRIPTING","courseDescription":"PHP is a widely-used general-purpose scripting language that is especially suited for server-side web development. Students learn to build web applications requiring server-side logic and to access SQL databases.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CSD 110 or CSD 111; CSD 112 Students who completed ITAD 111 and ITAD 112 meet the prerequisites.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"275","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9710,"days":"W","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Wu Z","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"297","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"IT PROJECT","courseDescription":"In this course students develop a real world software application, going through a complete application development life cycle, including analysis, design, specification, implementation, debugging, and deployment.","credits":3.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CS 143 and instructor premission","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"297","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9715,"days":"Th","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Anderson G","labFee":51.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"298","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"INTERVIEW/JOB SEARCH","courseDescription":"This course teaches technical interview preparation techniques and examines the job search process for employment in the software development field. Common strategies for a successful interview will be discussed. Students will practice solving interview problems.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: CSD 143 Students who completed CS 143 meet the prequisite.","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"298","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9720,"days":"W","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"GuerraHahn,M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"331","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"DATABASE MODELING\u0026DESIGN","courseDescription":"This course introduces relational database schema design using real-life data examples. Advanced data management topics are examined, including data modeling, normalization, analysis of query efficiency, usage of stored procedures, and triggers. Non-relational (NoSQL) databases used with Big Data are introduced and compared with RDMS.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CSD 138, CSD 321, MATH 220, and admission to the BAS IT:CSD program","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"331","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9725,"days":"W","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Komraz A","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"332","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"SOFTWARE PROJECT MANAGE","courseDescription":"This course teaches the fundamentals of software project management. Students learn how to manage a software development project from analyzing requirements through providing support: roles of stakeholders, methods of project planning, scheduling, risk analysis and mitigation, scope control, progress monitoring, and quality assurance. Modern techniques such as agile development are studied. Students learn to assess product readiness and manage ways to successfully complete a time-driven or feature-driven project. Different aspects of project readiness are analyzed from feature completeness and acceptance testing to properly documenting, globalizing, and marketing the product.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CSD 321 and admission to the BAS IT:CSD program","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"332","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9730,"days":"Th","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Finan J","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"335","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"ALGORITHMS \u0026 STRUCTURES","courseDescription":"Students study data structures, such as stacks, queues, hash tables, heaps, trees, and graphs, and use different algorithmic approaches to problem solving, such as simple recursion, backtracking, divide and conquer, greedy and brute force algorithms, and dynamic programming. Students analyze algorithm efficiency in terms of memory use and speed, using Big O notation for run-time performance estimation.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CS 143 and admission to the BAS IT:CSD program","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"335","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9735,"days":"T","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Abbott T","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"438","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"BIG DATA APP DEV","courseDescription":"Students are introduced to techniques and tools used to manage, process, and interact with massive datasets. The course explores non-relational (NoSQL) data storage for big data applications. The course covers topics such as distributed data storage, MapReduce, key value stores, stream processing, data mining, and basic statistical techniques to perform data analytics.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisites: CSD 331 and CSD 425","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"438","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9745,"days":"T","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"GuerraHahn,M","labFee":85.0}]},{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"480","quarterName":"Spring 21","courseTitle":"CAPSTONE PROJECT","courseDescription":"Students will design, implement and deploy a desktop, web, or mobile application. This course prepares students for employment at a software company, demonstrating a full software product development cycle: project management and design, algorithm development, coding, and quality assurance. This course may be completed as an internship at a software company.","credits":5.0,"preCoRequisites":"Prerequisite: Instructor permission","courseSections":[{"department":"CSD","courseNbr":"480","quarterName":"Spring 21","sectionCode":"R21","itemNbr":9750,"days":"W","timeLocation":"06:00 PM - 08:50 PM @ ZOOM","instructor":"Abbott T","labFee":85.0}]}]</string>
</resources>